Sonu Thomas

Kannur, Kerala, India



sonuthomas832@gmail.com



9446102896



linkedin.com/in/sonu-thomas-

Summary

I'm a Web designer and always a tech enthusiast too. I am experienced in using programming languages such as C, C++, JAVA, HTML5, CSS, JAVASCRIPT, JQUEREY to architect websites and much more from scratch. Since computer education is a vast field, I believe that open source material studies will be successful here. I want learn more programming languages and Achieve a good carrier in Tech industry

Experience



Web Designer

Freelance

Dec 2021 - Present (7 months +)

Photographer

ST JOSEPHS HSS VAYATTUPARAMBA Jun 2019 - Present (3 years 1 month +) School Photographer

Video Editor

ST JOSEPHS HSS VAYATTUPARAMBA Jun 2019 - Present (3 years 1 month +) School's Video Editor

Education



🤊 ST JOSEPH'S HSS VAYATTUPARAMBA

+1, Computer Science 2021 - 2023

ST JOSEPH'S HSS VAYATTUPARAMBA

10 SSLC Jun 2018 - Apr 2021

Licenses & Certifications



Brototype 100k Coding Challenge - Brototype

100KCC79797



Brototype Web Designing Challenge - Brototype

Skills

English • Presentations • Communication • Web Design • C (Programming Language) • C++ • JavaScript • HTML5 • Cascading Style Sheets (CSS) • Bootstrap

Honors & Awards

Rising Star Award - St Joseph's H S S Vayattuparamba Oct 2021